3stepstosearchenginesuccess.com 2011-06-29

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to 3StepsToSearchEngineSuccess.com is important to us.

At 3StepsToSearchEngineSuccess.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit DatingAdvisor.co.uk and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

By using this Website, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes will be posted on this page and visitors are encouraged to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

**Information Collected Automatically**

In some cases, we may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical information when you connect to our Website that is not personally identifiable information. Examples of this type of information include the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. Also, when you view our Website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Website to better match your interests and preferences. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

**Privacy Information for Persons 13 Years and Older**

We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address) through our Website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you. For example, if you choose to sign up for a newsletter, we will request your name and email address.

When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise:

We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services;

We employ other companies to perform certain functions on our behalf, such as processing orders and delivering packages, conducting surveys and sending you mailings regarding our products and these companies have access to your personal information and;

We may contact you regarding promotions and other offers regarding our products that may interest you.  
We do not now, and do not intend to, sell, rent or market personally identifiable information about you to third parties. We share information only with subsidiaries of this site and may use it to send you promotions and product information.

**Children Under 13**

Our Privacy Policy applies to children as well as adults. There are some extra precautions that we take, however, with respect to collecting information from children under 13.

We encourage parents and guardians to explore our Website with their children.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from your children under 13 on-line without first obtaining permission from the child’s parent or guardian.

Our Website does not offer activities that allow your child disclose your child’s personal information publicly (for example through chat rooms or message boards).

We do not share your child’s personally identifiable information with third parties.  
Please also note that we do not offer activities that require the ongoing collection and use of personally identifiable information provided by children.

**Use of Website and Website Material**

This Website is provided for your personal noncommercial use. You may not copy material from this Website for commercial use. You may copy material in limited quantities from this Website for your personal noncommercial use provided that our copyright notice is affixed to the copied material. We reserve the right to terminate, at any time, your permission to make personal copies of material from this Website.

You are prohibited from using this Website to post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, profane material, any material that infringes on any copyright, trademark or other proprietary right or any material that could constitute or encourage unlawful conduct. We may, from time to time, monitor or review material transmitted or posted using this Website and reserve the right to delete any material we deem inappropriate. This Website is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from any material transmitted or posted using this Website.

**Ownership of Intellectual Property**

All material on this website is copyrighted, either by us or third party providers. Notwithstanding any other term or condition in this agreement, We retains ownership to the copyright in this Website and all material from this Website unless otherwise indicated.

**Disclaimer**

Your use of this Website and material from this Website is at your own risk.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies** We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

**Third Party Advertisements** We also use third party advertisements on 3StepsToSearchEngineSuccess.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing UK based ads to someone in the UK, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing dating ads to someone who frequents dating sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Severed Provisions and Entire Agreement**

If any provision of this agreement is unenforceable, that provision shall be deemed severed from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions.

This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the subject matter.

We may modify these Terms of Use at any time and without notice. You are bound by any modifications and should therefore periodically visit this page to review Terms of Use to which you are bound.

I’ve made a post in the past listing what I thought were the most common SEO mistakes, but based on what I’ve experienced over the last few months, helping people with their SEO, this to me has to be one of the most common mistakes that people make. I’ve not talked about it at any [...]

* * *

Mark Ling’s AffiloJetPack is released on July 26th at 12noon. If you are thinking of buying it you probably want to read some AffiloJetPack reviews and learn a bit more about it to see whether or not it is right for you. It’s also worth knowing that many people are offering AffiloJetPack Bonuses for anyone [...]

* * *

If you are trying to optimize your website for the search engines it can be very easy to make mistakes, especially if you are new to SEO. I think the easiest way to learn how to optimize your website properly is to look at some common seo mistakes and learn from them. It is always [...]

* * *

Search Engine Optimization and Keyword research can be a complex area, especially if you are new to internet marketing. Understanding how to choose the best keywords for your website, how to optimize your website correctly for the search engines and how to get a higher search engine ranking can have a steep learning curve. You [...]

* * *

**[How Not to Get a Better Search Engine Rank – 7 Mistakes to Avoid](http://www.3stepstosearchenginesuccess.com/on-page-optimization/how-not-to-get-a-better-search-engine-rank-5-mistakes-to-avoid "Permanent Link to How Not to Get a Better Search Engine Rank – 7 Mistakes to Avoid")**

In most of my posts I have concentrated on different ways to get a better search engine rank. Today I’m going to talk about how not to get a better search engine rank. It is good to know what you need to do to improve your search engine ranking, but what about what you shouldn’t [...]

* * *
